http://www.hardwirellc.com/pages/privacy-policy

Skip to content
100 PACK FACE SHIELDS FOR ONLY $100 + FREE SHIPPING | $1.00 PER FACE SHIELD
Privacy Statement
Our Commitment To Privacy
At Hardwire, LLC, we are committed to protecting your privacy online. Our pledge is to safeguard any personal information that you provide us, and to make every reasonable effort to use this information only as you choose. We at Hardwire, LLC are taking a leadership role in assisting our customers and other businesses in understanding the importance of using your personal information appropriately.
Your Personal Information
Hardwire, LLC's primary goals in collecting personal information about you are, first, to give you a meaningful, enjoyable, and personalized website experience and, second, to facilitate the development of new products and services relevant to consumers like you. Personal information also allows us to provide better service to you by tailoring our communications to match your interests - deliver more of what you want and less of what you don't want.
Protecting Your Information
Hardwire, LLC implements a variety of administrative, managerial, and technical security measures to help protect your personal information. Hardwire, LLC has Internal Control Standards which relate specifically to the Handling of personal information. These include certain controls to help safeguard the information we collect online. Hardwire, LLC employees are trained to understand and comply with these controls and we communicate our Privacy Notice, practices and guidelines to our employees. However, while we strive to protect your personal information, you must also take steps to protect your information. We urge you to take every precaution to protect your personal information while you are on the Internet.
choosing a selection results in a full page refresh
